(司法事务司 路环监狱)
"Secretary of Judiciary of the Coloane Jail"
喂，他是谁？
Hey, who is he?
他叫黄师虎，是个老千
He is Master Wong, he is a swindler.
他在这里很受欢迎的
He is very popular here.
比四大天王还要厉害
He is greater than the Great Four.
他的狗马贴士经常中
He tips on horse races are always sharp.
我可不大相信
I don't believe it!
我的绰号叫赌场包青天
My nickname is the Judge of the Casino.
在我跟前，没有人能出千的
No one dares to cheat in front of me.
- 签名吧… - 够了，明天才签吧
- Give me an autograph. - Enough, we'll continue tomorrow.
喂，听说你是个老千
Hey, they said that you are a famous swindler.
什么老千呀，人家胡诌而已
It is a rumor, that's all.
你真够嚣张，我跟你赌一把
You are really cocky! Let me play a hand with you.
你输了的话，我每天打你十拳
If you lose, I get to give you ten punches a day.
打足一年
And, for a whole year.
我输了的话，免费让你抽香烟一年
If I lose, you get to smoke free for a whole year.
太凶险了，不要吧
Very risky! Please don't!
你说什么？
What did you say?
你想怎么赌法？
What are the rules?
选中Ace就算你赢
If you can find the Ace, you win.
哪一张是Ace？
Which one is Ace?
反正都是赌，注码大一点吧
It's gambling anyway, let's bet more.
我输了，往后一年
If I lose, you get to hit me with a stick...
每天让你用棍子打一百下
hundred times a day for the whole next year.
你输了，让我用棍子打一下就是了
If you lose, just let me hit you once with the stick.
- 好的 - 一言为定
- OK. - We have a deal!
这张…不是
This one...No.
这张…也不是
This one...No!
这张吧
This one must be Ace.
真棒…
Very good...
拿棍子来
Give me the stick.
真棒，黄师虎真棒
Awesome! Master Wong is great!
算了吧，我哪有胆量打你呢？
Forget it! Do you think I dare to hit you?
请我抽一口烟就算了吧
Just give me a smoke, OK?
好的…请随便
OK...Help yourself.
谢谢
Thanks!
黄师虎真棒…
Master Wong, you are awesome...
千面人呼叫梁宽…
The Masked-man calling Leung Fon...
梁宽收到了，请说吧
Leung Fon is here, over.
学校里有没有状况？
What is the situation now in school?
暂时水静河飞
Very quiet.
线报说，匪徒今天会来绑架
We're informed that the kidnappers...
大地产商何生的千金何小姐
will come to kidnap the Billionaire Ho's daughter.
你要全力保护她
You have to protect her by all means.
长官，你放心
Sir, don't worry!
何小姐一定不会少一根汗毛的
Miss Ho will be safe under my protection.
这个世上真是人种复杂
There are so many kinds of people.
很多人自以为天生丽质
Someone thinks that because her family is rich...
家境富裕就跋扈嚣张
then she can be proud to do whatever she wants.
但愿她上街就被人浇镪水
I hope she would be dumped acid on her face.
有没有看见前排那个戴眼镜的三八？
Do you see that bitch with glasses at the front row?
她老是跟我抬扛
She always challenges me!
给我抓她去厕所狠狠的揍一顿
Take her to the bathroom and teach her a lesson.
我只是来保护你而已
I am here to protect you only.
你惹的其他是非，你自己料理好了
Please take care of your own problem.
我不是你的打手
I am not your hitman.
我要是有什么意外，是不是由你负责
If anything happens to me, are you going to be responsible?
我要是你老爸，我一定喂你吃大便
If I were your dad, I would have fed you shit.
好
Good!
它在哪里？
Where is she?
梁宽同学，你在干嘛？
Leung Fon, what are you doing?
同学间切磋一下而已
We are trying to get to know each other better.
切磋功课是这样子的吗？
Is this the proper way?
切磋功夫
We are studying kung fu.
好痛…
It hurts...
你别再念书了，去日本发展吧
Why don't you quit school and go start a career in Japan.
去了…
I will...
出去
Out.
(我以后不再性骚扰女同学)
"I won't harrass the female classmates anymore."
长官，是不是有情况？
Sir, is something happen?
紧急情况，你要在一分钟之内上天台
Emergency, go up to the roof in one minute.
一定要在一分钟之内，要不然就糟了
Remember, in one minute!
长官，天台没有人
Sir, is something wrong?
你马上赶到楼下看看地上有没有蚂蚊
Hurry down to the ground floor and check if there're any ants on the floor.
是
Yes Sir.
报告，地上没有蚂蚊
Sir, there is no ant on the floor.
那你上天台看看有没有草蜢
Go up to the roof and check if there are any grasshoppers.
是
Yes Sir.
长官，天台真的有很多草蜢
Sir, there are lots of grasshoppers on the roof.
解散
Dismiss.
四大匪徒先生
Gentlemen.
请问你们怎么知道我们是卧底？
Can you tell me how you know that I am an undercover?
你看，警方派卧底假扮学生
Look, a police acting as a student to protect rich man's daughter.
保护富豪子女
又是狗仔队
Reporters again.
我以后一定要多化妆才行
I have to improve my make-up skill.
走吧
Let's go.
干嘛？
What?
放了她
Let her go.
怎么你没事的？
What the hell? Why are you alright?
本来我快要累死了，幸亏…
I was almost exhausted. But luckily...
我用了Yeah
I used Yeah!
我马上变得精神奕奕，正点
I've become very energetic. Very good.
放了她
Let her go.
快走…
Hurry...
别动
Don't move.
快走…
Go...
长官，要不要给你擦跌打药？
Sir, do you want some herbal oil?
不用了，我有药用胶布
It's OK, I have bandaid.
那就好了
That's better.
瓦斯？
Gas?
整个房间都是瓦斯看你还敢不敢开枪
The whole room is loaded with gas. I dare you to shoot.
如果我开枪
If I shoot,
枪口所产生的火花就会引爆瓦斯
the gun will generate sparks which will start an explosion.
这房间就会爆炸，我该怎么办呢？
The whole room will explode. What should I do?
我很怕参加四乘一百接力赛
I am scared to run the 4 x 100 relay.
因为，我不想是最后一个到终点
Because I don't like to finish last.
你知不知道我们的对手最怕的是什么
Do you know what our opponents scare the most?
怕什么呢？
What?
怕你嘛，你的臭狐臭死了
It's you! Your armpit stinks.
他们一定不敢追近你
They are afraid to get close to you.
幸亏我随身带备了“爆光”柠檬茶
Luckily I carry around with me a box of "Silencer" lemon tea.
长官，我已经成功保护了何千金小姐
Sir, I have successfully stopped Miss Ho from being kidnapped.
拜托你
Please don't send me to do this kind of low-class undercover case again.
以后别再派我去做低级卧底工作
因为我已经装过律师、医生、护士…
I have acted as lawyer, doctor, nurse...
瘾君子、小混混、学生…
Druggy, gangster, student...
张学友、刘德华、黎明…
Jacky Chan, Andy Lau, Leon Lai...
甚至是黄夏蕙
Even that scary old lady Elizabeth Taylor.
我真不希望再做鸡毛皮的任务了
I don't want to do this kind of stupid case again.
你明天到我办公室再说吧
We will discuss it in my office tomorrow morning.
长官，我决定不再做小任务了
Sir, I have decided not to take on easy jobs.
你看，我一表人才
Look at me, I am gifted.
一看就知道我是干大事的
I should be carrying out some very big case.
你对我有什么不满意尽管跟我说
Just tell me everything you don't like about me.
你要我将头发弄直，我照办
You want my hair to go straight, and I'll follow your order.
但是…长官…
But...Sir...
长官，怎么你没精打彩的？
Sir, how come you don't seem happy?
这混旦真够跩
You bastard have got some guts.
早晚我放下我的家伙狠狠的揍他一顿
I will soon put down my gun and kick his ass.
你等着瞧吧
Wait for it.
我的绰号叫千面人嘛
My nickname is Masked-man.
以后别再说我的坏话了
Don't talk shit about me again.
长官，你再不派我去做大事
Sir, if you don't let me do something more challenging.
我辞职不干
I am going to quit.
收好你的家伙才跟我说吧
We will talk again after you put away your things first.
长官，无论如何
Sir, no matter what,
你将这件大案子给我吧
you have to let me handle this big case.
我一定会办得妥妥当当的
I will get it done.
长官，你跟我说话吧
Sir, talk to me.
神经病
Crazy!
我知道你就是千面人了，你耍我而已
I know you are the Masked-man. You are fooling me.
长官，我做了警察七年
Sir, I have been a cop for seven years.
智勇双全又够老实
I am honest and smart.
多年来我只得一个女朋友
I only have one girlfriend for all these years.
我真的连召妓也没试过
I've never slept with a hooker before.
只有一次我喝多了，上了按摩院
The only time I went to a massage place because I was drunk.
还碰到了家英哥呢
I saw brother Kai Ying!
我真的是个超级无敌好警察
I am a super, good, and nice police.
你不是我上司早点说嘛
Damn, tell me earlier that you're not my boss.
真被你害惨了
You've dragged me to deep shit.
你明明猜对了，但又不相信自己
You guessed it right, but you don't trust yourself.
你怎能去对付大老千法拉利呢？
How can you go against the Swindler Ferrari?
法拉利？
Ferrari?
不错，就是刮钱比索罗斯还要厉害
Yes, this cheater makes money faster than Soros.
说谎能力比克林顿还强的超级大老千
This cheater lies better than Clinton.
是那个绰号肉面飞龙万人迷的法拉利
He is the Handsome Dragon Ferrari.
近年他专门替老外基金经理搞风搞雨
Recently he helps the foreigners to crush the stock market.
又办了一张报纸诋毁香港
He has a newspaper which always harms Hong Kong's reputation.
又在金融市场刮钱，又做翻版生意
He steals money from the stock market. And sells pirate VCD too.
更令人痛恨的
The worst thing is that...
所有美女都给他泡了
he gets all the beautiful girls.
只剩下侏罗纪给我们
And leave the ugly ones for us.
单是这一条已经是死罪了
He should be executed for this.
长官，不用再说了
Sir, don't worry,
我一定给你抓他回来
I will go catch him for you.
好，你打动了我，我派你去
OK! You moved me. I will send you.
如果成功了，你一定能升职
If you are successful, you will be promoted.
谢谢，长官
Thank you, Sir.
你猜猜我买了什么给你吃？
Guess what I've bought for you?
家香鸡嘛，难道会是烧鹅吗？
Kentucky fried chicken!
我差不多两个星期没见你了
I haven't seen you for two weeks.
别耍我了，脱掉它吧
Don't you try to trick me, take off your mask.
你说什么？
What are you talking about?
你怎么了？痛死我了      有东西吃吗
- What are you doing? It hurts. - I am hungry, anything to eat?
是…
Yes...
对不起，我以为你是我的上司嘛
Sorry, I thought you were my boss.
去你的，我跟你谈了七年恋爱
I have been in love with you for seven years,
你居然认不得我
and you can't recognize me!
七年你也不习惯而已
You're not get used to it, that's all.
别生气嘛，到底什么事呢？
Don't get mad! What's wrong?
我姐夫下星期生日，你要陪我去澳门
My brother-in-law will celebrate his birthday. You've to go with me.
你大姐的老公，我们很少来往
I don't know your brother-in-law that well.
你总应该要见一下我大姐嘛
You should at least go meet my sister.
看情况，因我接了一个很重要的任务
We will see! I have accepted a very important case.
什么任务？
What case?
她是谁？
Who is she?
我也不知道，可能是我的上司吧
I don't know! May be my boss.
明天早上九点正在海滩见
See you tomorrow morning at 9 at the beach.
上天是很公平的
God is fair to me.
以我做卧底的天分，加上美貌与智慧
I was born to be an undercover. With my handsome look and wisdom.
终于得到对付法拉利这个重要的任务
I finally get to go against tough opponent like Ferrari.
在这个美丽的早上
In this beautiful morning.
我来到这个优美的沙滩
I came to this beautiful beach.
混旦…快给我滚
Asshole...Leave.
由于约我到沙滩见面的人还没出现
Since the person I am supposed to meet hasn't showed up yet.
所以，我决定先玩一下水上摩托车
So, I've decided to try water cycling.
这妞正点
This girl is so cute.
看见她，我有一种很清凉的感觉
When I saw her, I have a very fresh feeling.
就好像…
It's like...
先生，你会不会开摩托车的？
Sir, don't you know how to use this machine?
当然会，你真三八
Of course! You stupid!
算我不对了，麻烦你给我叫救护车吧
It's my fault! Please call an ambulance for me.
你真麻烦
You are a trouble to me!
你好
Hello.
我可以要你的电话号码吗？
Can I have your number?
走吧
Go.
再见
Good bye.
(去你的)
"Fuck you."
你真机灵
You are smart.
你给我粗话跟给我你的名字都是一样
Giving me your name is same as a curse.
你叫什么名字？
What is your name?
我叫初恋
My name is First Love.
初恋？
First Love?
初恋这个名字，实在太清新脱俗了
The name First Love is very sweet.
她令我觉得少年十五二十时
She reminds me of the feelings I had when I was still a teenager.
那种初恋的感觉
每个男人一生中都梦寐以求的
Every man dreams about this...First love!
死胖子，小心我宰了你
Fat boy! Want me to kill you and barbecue with your body fat?
用你的肥油来炸鸡翅膀
火龙哥，我被人欺负
Brother Lon, someone is picking on me.
你唬我吗？
Are you trying to scare me?
你就是梁宽？
You must be Leung!
火龙哥？就是你约我来的
Brother Lon? Are you the person I am supposed to meet?
你就是肉面飞龙
So you must be Handsome Dragon Ferrari's assistant, Brother Lon.
法拉利的得力助手火龙哥
这胖子真够机灵
You are very smart, fat boy.
我老板就在那儿
My boss is over there.
拉哥
Brother Ferrari.
你倒算一表人才，我给你一个好任务
You seem to be a useful person. I will give you a good assignment.
拉哥吩咐，我赴汤蹈火都会办妥的
I'll try all my best.
你先跟我儿子去玩一会儿
Go play with my son.
你输了我要接受大惩罚
If you lose, you will have to face cruel punishment.
小胖哥，你要怎么罚我尽管说吧
Please tell me what punishment I'll receive.
不要，会弄出人命的
No! Someone will get killed.
走
Let's go!
真幸运，太感谢你了，龙哥
Very lucky! Thank you, Brother Lon.
不客气
No problem.
老板要你去揍那胖子一顿
My boss wants you to beat up that fat boy.
我跟他无怨无仇，很难下手
He didn't do anything to me. It's hard for me to hit him.
你到底去不去？
Are you going to do it?
当然去
Of course.
那就是了
OK.
你打我老板？
You hit my boss?
算了吧…揍他一两个小时就饶了他吧
Forget it...Just give him a beating for one or two hours.
法拉利，怎么他想揍你？
Ferrari, why does he want to hurt you?
从我致力为新界妇女争取合法地位后
Ever since I fought for the woman in the NT. for their legal rights,
一直都有很多人视我为眼中钉
many people started to hate me.
我经常都被人暗算
People try to assassinate me.
幸亏你有保镖
Luckily you have many good bodyguards.
我的经费不够，不能再雇用保镖了
Now I don't have enough money, I can't hire any more bodyguard.
你没钱？我有，五百万够不够？
You have no money, but I have! Is five million enough for you?
我怎可以花你的钱呢？
How can I use your money?
你我何分彼此呢？
Don't worry about it.
明天来我公司取支票吧
Come to my office tomorrow and pick up the check.
他就是法拉利？
He is Ferrari, isn't he?
对，所以这场戏我们一定要演下去
Yes! So we have to finish this scene together.
老板，怎么处置他？
Boss, what should we do with him?
对不起
Sorry!
你就是阿宽？
You must be Leung!
是，拉哥
Yes, Ferrari.
你以后就跟我吧，肥猪王会教你办事
Follow me from now on. Fat Pig will tell you what to do.
多谢…拉哥
Thanks, Ferrari.
今天晚上你做看更
You get the night shift tonight.
黑社会果然是黑社会
This must be money saving gangsters.
用不着这么早就关灯嘛
Why do they turn off all lights so early!
希望你们跌一个狗吃屎
Hope you all fall and die.
初恋小姐
Miss First Love.
不要吵
Shut up.
这种不三不四的地方
You are a nice girl,
不适合你这种女儿家来的
you shouldn't come to this kind of scary place.
我下载了法拉利的犯罪证据后我就走
I will leave after I download the criminal records of Ferrari.
原来他有这么多仇人
So many people hate him.
我爸爸的钱就是被他骗去的
He tricked all my dad's money.
害得我们家散人亡
My whole family was destroyed by him.
如果你聪明的话就给我闭嘴
You better shut up and stand aside.
不然就把你都干掉
Or I will kill you too.
不用急，你慢慢看吧，我替你把风
Don't worry, take your time, I will watch out for you.
谁？
Who is there?
我不可以见死不救的
I can't stay and watch you die,
我是个男子汉大丈夫
I am a righteous gentleman.
替你吃了他们那一脚吧
Let me be your shield.
别动…我抓到她了
Don't move...l've got her.
我来抓你
I am going to catch you.
抓到了
I've got her.
快胁持着我
Take me as your hostage.
不要动，不然就干掉他
Don't move! Or I am going to kill him.
不要…别追      别动
- No...Don't come after me. - Don't move!
很危险，我死定了
It's very dangerous, I am going to die.
不要追
Don't come after me.
看看
Look...
流血
Blood!
你怕吗？
Are you scared?
一点点…一点点我不会怕的
A little bit... I am not scared of that little blood.
你看够了没有？
Have you finished looking at my body?
差不多了
Almost.
有什么我可以帮忙的？
What can I help you?
帮我擦血吧
Wipe off the blood for me.
我扶你到房间休息好吗？
I will help you to my room and get some rest, OK?
我进去房间之后，你又会说…
After I going to your room with you, you will say...
不如我陪你睡一下，对不对？
Can I sleep with you for a while, right?
我有什么能帮忙的话你尽管说
If you need any help, just tell me.
我现在到你的房间休息一下
I am going to your room and get some rest.
如果你敢进来的话
If you dare to come in,
我就把你眼睛给挖出来
I will put out both of your eyes.
你变态的，房间这么多厕所
You are insane! You have so many toilets in your room.
连我这种正人君子都几乎憋不住
Even a gentleman like me can't hold myself down.
干嘛你半夜三更来这里？
Why do you come in the midnight?
我传呼你差不多一个星期也没有回覆
I called you for a whole week and you never answered my calls.
我有正经事要办嘛，你别管我这么多
I am working right now. Don't mind me.
你猜猜我买了什么给你吃？
Guess what have I brought you?
必胜客难道会卖叉烧包吗？大笨旦
Pizza Hut only sells pizza. You are so stupid.
你说过女人不用太精明的
You said that women don't have to be smart.
我喜欢…
I like it...
晚了，回家吧
Good night! Go home.
用不着这么急吧      快回家
- What's the rush? - Go home.
让我坐一会儿吧
Let me sit for a while.
既然你不想回家
If you don't want to go home,
我们就在这里做爱好吗？
let's make love then?
不…
No...
你还记得明天是我姐夫生日
You still remember that tomorrow is my brother-in-law's birthday...
我们要去澳门吗？
and we have to go to Macau, right?
那好吧，明天我陪你去澳门
OK! I will go to Macau with you tomorrow.
以后我们就别太死板
Let's not have bored games in future.
我们玩性变态游戏…
Let's try S & M from now on...
跟动物一起做爱好不好？
Like making love with animals, OK?
好的      我们现在就去买船票吧
- OK. - Let's go buy the boat tickets now.
去吧
Let's go.
等一下…待会我跟你玩，你要小心
Wait...I will play with you later... Be careful.
大姐      Pizza
- Sister. - Pizza.
他是我男朋友阿宽
He is my boyfriend, Leung Fon.
一表人才
He looks smart.
谢谢，自己人来坐吧
Thanks! Come on, sit.
大伯公、二舅父、七姨妈
Uncle, uncle Yee, Aunt Seven.
我给你们介绍Pizza的男朋友
This Pizza's boyfriend.
发型虽然太土气
His hair is ugly, he is stupid as well...
又穷得要命，又没什么文化…
He is poor, he is not civilized...
性能力又十分差
He is weak in bed.
不过还算一表人才，对不对？
But he is nice, right?
我说话太率直了，来…玩牌吧
I am very straight forward, come on...Let's play.
你别生气，你是个人才
Don't get mad. You are a nice fellow.
我知道
I know.
忽然间，我全身的毛孔都竖起来了
Suddenly, I felt danger.
我发觉在我的背后
I felt a very strong force rushing in from the door.
有一股很猛烈很厉害的能量正涌进来
直觉告诉我
The force tells me that...
有一个响当当的人物正进来
a very important person is coming in.
真棒…
Awesome...
装模作样的
La-di-da.
老公
Hubby.
老婆      老公
- Honey. - Hubby.
不要
No.
早跟你说过
I told you,
当我的左右护法在我身旁的时候
when my bodyguards are standing next to me,
任何人都不能接近我，你记性真差
no one is allowed to get close to me. Your memory is very bad.
对不起，老公
Sorry, honey.
真棒…恭喜…
Yeah...Congratulation...
对不起，今天不是我的生日
Sorry! Today is not my birthday.
其实是我老爸的忌辰
Today is my father's death day.
我老婆弄错而已，所以大家别太高兴
My wife made a mistake. So everyone doesn't have to be this happy.
不过大家亦不用太伤心
But you don't have to be sad too.
基本上我老爸其实是个大混旦
My dad was an asshole when he was alive.
他打劫、杀人、强奸无所不为
He robbed, killed and raped.
他的死，我觉得其实是社会之福
His death is good to the society.
那就好了
That's good.
不过…我老爸其实也很疼我
But...My dad loved me a lot.
他去打劫银行
He robbed the bank,
其实只是想给我买一辆玩具车
because he wanted to buy me a toy car.
杀人亦只是对方说我不够英俊
He killed because that person said I was not handsome.
强奸妇女亦只因我跟他说我想要妹妹
He raped because I told him I wanted a sister.
我…我老爸其实是一个慈父
My dad was a great father.
你姐夫真有一手，耍得他们团团转
Your brother-in-law is something. They are all fooled by him.
当然，他是千…
Of course, he is a sw...
千什么？千什么呢？
What? What is he?
他是千禧年庆祝筹委会的会长
He is the supervisor of the Millennium Celebration.
我真想你，来打个吻吧
I really miss you! Come on, give me a kiss.
你进步不少，你吻得他舌头也开了花
You improved a lot. Your kiss made his tongue tie a knot.
那还用说，死相
Of course, you punk!
怎么不见了我的好朋友？      谁？
- Where is my best friend? - Who?
就是谁敢拔我一条汗毛
The one who will protect me until his death, Brother Five.
都会被他大卸八块的龙五
龙五？龙五也会来吗？
Brother Five? Did he come?
说起来，你最近多了很多白头发
Hey, you have lots of white hair recently.
救命…
Help...
你快去帮忙
Go help her!
怎么你又不去呢？
Why didn't you go?
停手…
Stop...
(停)
"Stop"
他就是龙五？怎么叫他也不停手？
He is Brother Five? How come he won't stop when you tell him to?
当然了，他叫“聋五”嘛
Of course! He is brother Deaf.
是个聋子，当然听不到嘛
He is deaf and he can't hear anything.
好兄弟…
Good friend...
(你老婆好吗)
"How's your wife?"
我说过不再说我老婆嘛，不说了
I told you not to talk about my wife again. No more.
其实是这样的
The truth is, couple of days ago,
几天前，我因为膀胱发炎进了医院
I went to the hospital because of cystitis.
等了很久我老婆都没有来
I've waited for a long time but my wife didn't show up.
只见到记者
I only saw reporters.
他们将我的前尘旧事都翻出来说
They started to talk about my past,
想不到我老婆的演技比我更厉害
I can't believe that my wife's acting skill is better than mine.
正所谓“老婆就白白胖胖”
Like the old saying "The wife is living happily,"
“老公就皮黄骨瘦”
"and the husband is working poorly."
今天我正所谓人老色衰，老婆跑路了
Today, my body is very weak and my wife is leaving me.
现在所有人都说我儿子很帅
Now everybody say my son is handsome.
我怀疑他不是我亲生的，真可怜
I'm suspecting that he is not my own son. I am very poor!
你姐夫没手的吗？
Is your brother-in-law armless?
不是
No!
怎么他身旁那两个人像个连体婴一样
How come the two persons next to him are like they are connected to him?
还有，炎炎夏日
And, it is very hot right now,
居然还将豹皮挂在脖子上
but he is wearing cheetah skin on his neck.
他的扮相太夸张了吧
Why does he dress so loudly?
自摸，门前清四归一独独
I won! It's a big slam!
象眼一摸五
没什么大不了，才一百一十三番而已
No big deal, 113 folds.
不是吧
Are your kidding?
你姐夫到底是什么人？
What is your brother-in-law?
你该知道我最憎恨老千的
You know that I hate swindler.
中，我确是一个老千
Right! I am a swindler.
这里的人十居其九都是老千
9 out of 10 persons here are swindlers.
你就是Pizza的男朋友？
You must be Pizza's boyfriend?
中，我是Pizza的男人
Right! I am her man.
未请教？
Your name is?
梁宽，未请教？
Fon! And yours?
黄师虎
Master Wong.
原来就是那个人称赌场鬼见愁
You must be that famous Jinx in the casino.
遇神骗神遇佛骗佛的千王之王黄师虎
You will cheat on anyone, the best swindler alive, Master Wong.
不敢…朋友给我面子而已
Thank you! It's a flattering to me, that's all.
连摸牌都由其他人效劳
You need people to get the domino for you.
你这个千王的架子似乎太大了
Who do you think you are, a king?
师虎哥暂时住在监狱
Master Wong is still serving his sentence in jail.
今天是他宴客
Today, he is the boss,
故此向狱长申请了两小时的假期
he applied for two hours leave.
吃完了甜品之后，我们就带他回去
After dessert, we will have to take him back.
不过，他不能接触任何人
But, no one can contact him.
原来是个囚犯
So, he is a prisoner.
阿宽…
Fon...
男人说话，女人闭嘴
I am talking, you shut up.
不要紧，难得今天高兴
Don't worry! Since we are happy today.
我们赌一把十三张吧
Let's play cards.
我不赌钱的
I don't like to gamble.
闹着玩而已
Just for fun.
我做庄，五十二张牌任你先选
I will be the banker, you get to pick the cards first.
你赢了的话我输十万块
If you win I will give you $100,000.
你输了的话
If you lose,
只跟我的女人打个吻就好了
you have to kiss my woman.
好，我就看看你有什么本事
OK! Let me see how good you really are.
行了吗？
Are you done?
三张Ace在前面，先赢三注
Three Aces in front, I win 3 points first.
第二关是红心同花顺，赢十注
Straight heart flush in the middle, I win 10 more points.
黑桃同花顺押尾，总共赢你十八注
Straight spade flush at the end. I will 18 points.
三张八
Three 8s.
中间和最后都是同花顺
Straight flush in the middle and on the last row.
前中后都是我赢
I'm the winner!
不，前面三张Ace赢我三注
No! You win with three Aces in front. You win 3 points.
尾关你有一张Ace又赢我五注
You beat me with an ace on the last row. Which you'll win 5 more points.
但中间那一关我们一样
For the middle row, we break even.
我的花比你的大
Spade beats heart.
十三张不算花的
No, the rules of this game don't state that.
我做庄，所以我赢你的
I am the dealer, so I win.
次关算两倍，我赢你十注
The middle row counts double. So I have 10 points.
对比之下我还赢你两注
The final is 10 to 8. I win you by 2 points.
不用死，输了只要打个吻就行了
Fine! I will kiss your women then.
叫我的马子出来
Get my women.
你好      甜心
- Hi! - Honey.
吻我吧
Kiss me.
宽哥，动嘴吧
Brother Leung, go ahead.
罚我其他事好不好？
Can I do something else?
你看看她们俩都怀了身孕
Look at them, two of them are pregnant.
中间那个看似长期缺氧的
The one in the middle is like she is lacking of oxygen.
不如…再赌一把好不好？
Why don't we play again?
行，既然你这么说
OK!
你跪下来给我舔干净鞋面就算了
Get down on your knees and lick my shoes clean.
姐夫，别这样嘛
Brother-in-law, please!
年轻人，嚣张跋扈
Young man, you are cocky!
被自己人教训总比被外人耍好得多
It's better for me to teach you a lesson than being tricked by outsiders.
我舔
I will lick it.
很恶心
It sucks!
怎么样？
So?
要是你厚颜无耻的话，我们就算了吧
If you can't do it, let's forget it.
甜甜的？
It's sweet?
傻小子，蜘蛛网是棉花糖
Silly! The spider web is marshmallow.
小粒粒是糖粉，屎呢…
The little dots are candies. The shit...
真的是屎
That's really shit!
混旦，连我也作弄吗？
Asshole! You tricked me too?
别生气嘛，他们跟你闹着玩而已
Don't get mad! They are playing with you, that's all.
闹着玩？
Playing with me?
以后别让我在香港碰上你
Don't let me see you in Hong Kong.
你别再来澳门找我就行了
Don't come to Macau and look for me.
快给我擦了它吧
Wipe it off for me.
你将他们全塞进我的嘴巴了
You are pushing that rest of them into my mouth!
你斗不过我姐夫的
You can't beat my brother-in-law.
这次他要你给他舔鞋子
He wanted you to lick his shoe this time.
下次我可不知道他要你舔什么
I don't know what he will want you to lick next time.
我跟你说，这个仇我一定要报
Let me tell you, he is going to pay for this.
你闻一下我的嘴巴还臭不臭吧？
Does my mouth still stink?
我跟你说
Let me tell you, in my whole life,
我这辈子最痛恨那些小老千
I hate swindler the most.
我姐夫是大老千
My brother-in-law is the best swindler!
大？怎及得上我要办的案子呢？
Best? He is just a small potato!
要是被我抓到法拉利
If I can arrest Ferrari,
我最少会连升两级
I will at least be promoted by two ranks.
法拉利？我大姐说过他很厉害的
Ferrari? My sister said that he is great.
你怎斗得过他？
How can you beat him?
我斗不过他？
Why can't I beat him?
我是警察，我一定能抓到他
I am a cop, I can do it.
你用不着这么激动吧
You don't have to get so excited.
我只是关心你而已
I am worried about you, that's all.
这样吧，快替我留点子孙根吧
Why don't we do something together?
不行
No.
你说过从澳门回来之后就跟我干的
You promised to do it with me after we come back from Macau.
又用这个？
Use this again?
戴着它，世界就变得空泛和欠真实感
If I wear that, I will lose all the feelings.
确是很欠真实感，那么你去不去买？
Yes. But are you going to go buy it or not?
很晚了
It's very late.
你是男人嘛，你一定有办法的
You are a man, you can do it.
我去试试看吧
I will try.
你打电话到成人台，预订那出…
Call the adult channel, and order that movie...
很难订的那出…
The...Bra.
午夜…胸围，要老外主演那出
The one which a black guy starring in it.
怎么搞的？这间便利店这么早就关门
What the hell? All the stores are closed already.
半夜三更，哪里可以买到安全套呢？
In the midnight, where can I buy condom?
保鲜纸也管用的
Transparent film will do.
你好，我已经将我们俩的事跟她说了
Hello! I have told her the things between us.
你说了什么？
What did you say?
下贱
Asshole!
你可真不对
You are wrong.
你怪我跟她说我们有一腿吗？
You are at me for telling her the adultery between us?
我怪你还没跟我发生关系就先跟她说
I am mad at you for telling her before we have sex.
有机会的
You will have a chance.
但是…你要帮我对付法拉利
But...You have to help me go against Ferrari.
我也这么想，但是我还没想到办法
I want to! But I don't have any idea.
我可有办法，但你要受一点点儿痛苦
I do. If you can stand a little pain.
你可不可以先给我一点快乐呢？
Can you give me some happiness first?
改天吧
Some other day.
先打一个吻好吗？
Give me a kiss first, OK?
那你可不可以让我踢一下你的那话儿
Can you let me kick your dick?
打扫一下就可以
You can clean it up.
下流
Asshole.
诚哥，这宗生意我们就这么说定了
Brother Sing, it's deal, OK?
我全赖你了
I am counting on you.
今天晚上别回去
Don't go back tonight.
明天早上我们去打高尔夫球
We will go play golf tomorrow.
谁怕谁？
OK.
失陪了，带李老板去休息
Excuse me! Take Mr. Lee to rest.
请随便…
Help yourself...
这边请
This way please.
老大，我终于将那飞天蠄蟧抓回来了
Boss, I finally captured the Spider Woman.
不是你给她抓了去吗？
Didn't she kidnap you?
最初的确是的
At first, yes!
但是…这女的原来是个大笨旦
But...She is a very stupid thief!
我装死她就以为我真的死了
I acted like I was dead and she believed me.
我趁她不在意，从后拉她的头发
When she was not paying attention to me, I pulled her hair.
在她胸口狂轰，我小时候练过猴拳嘛
And hit her chest hardly. I learned monkey fist when I was a kid.
想偷我电脑的资料，跟我说就行了
Trying to steal my computer files? All you have to do is ask me.
肥猪王，抓她到我房间去
Fat Pig, take her to my room.
放开我…
Let me go...
放开我
长官，我是阿宽
Sir, I am Leung.
我在法拉利家里偷取他电脑里的资料
I am in Ferrari's house. I am stealing his computer file.
这么厉害？
Really?
我牺牲很大的
I sacrificed a lot.
你快召集所有兄弟
Call all the available units,
飞虎队、解放军统统都叫来
soldiers and whatever to come here.
要是来迟了
If you come late,
我梦中情人就会被人占了便宜
my dream lover will get raped.
我做人就会很低潮了
If that happens, I will be very sad.
我情绪会变得很寂寞
I will become very lonely.
好的，大不了我不化妆就赶来
OK! I will not put on my mask then.
好的
OK.
初恋她…
First Love...
你不要过来…不要过来
Don't come any closer.
死胖子，竟敢摧毁我的初恋
Fat ass! How dare you touch my First Love.
我要干掉你这混旦
I have to kill you asshole!
谁打我？
Who hit me?
你是谁？
Who are you?
我问你是谁？
很痛      她是谁？
- It hurts? - Who is she?
她是我老婆，还会是谁…
She is my wife! Who do you think she is?
我的初恋呢？
First love?
初恋？初恋是人生最宝贵的
Everybody treasures first love.
你的初恋怎会在我的床上呢？混旦
How would your First Love be in my bed? Asshole!
真是对不起
Sorry!
对不起？你去死吧
Sorry? Go to hell.
初恋…
First love...
这房子的空调真够冷
It is very cold in this house.
你是不是我上司？
Are you my boss?
我说过没时间化妆嘛
I told you I don't have time to put on my mask.
我找不到初恋
I can find First Love.
我也找不到我的初恋
I can't find my first love too!
人生就是这样子了，罪证呢？
This is life. Where is the evidence?
你们这么多人来我家
Do you have any warrant?
到底有没有搜查令？
我的初恋呢？
Where is my First Love?
你到底在说什么？
What the hell are you talking about?
你是谁？
Who are you?
警察，香港警察梁宽
Police! Hong Kong police, Leung.
奉命卧底来抓这死胖子的
I am an undercover who is sent to arrest this fat boy.
我要见你的上司
I want to see your superior.
我就是了，但这黑锅我不替他背的
I am. But I won't be responsible for his mistake.
你不认识我吗？我就是李老板
You don't know me? I am Mr. Lee.
我要投诉你滥用暴力
I want to complain that he abused violence.
将我的眼睛打伤
He injured my eye.
还有，用非法的手段
And he illegally broke us apart...
影响我们夫妻俩的合法性生活
when we were having sex.
你到底要找什么？我不认识他的
What are you looking for? I don't know him.
你不认识我？
You don't know me?
我跟你的死胖儿子玩拔河
I played with your fat son.
他四个人欺负我一个人
Four of them picked on me.
我的儿子不是个胖子
My son is not a fat boy.
老公，发生了什么事？
What's going on, honey?
不用担心，我会应付了
Take it easy! I can handle it.
你耍我吗？你老婆是个中国人
Are you playing me? Your wife is a Chinese.
我们是有结婚证书的
We have a marriage certificate.
长官，他说谎而已，伸冤
Sir, he is lying, I am innocent!
这是什么磁碟？
What kind of disk is this?
里面所载的全部是电脑病毒
It contains nothing but computer virus.
警方重案组整个资料库都被它洗掉
It erased everything we saved in the central computer.
现在全都变了电脑游戏
The whole system became a giant video game station.
长官，这是我一时大意
Sir, I made a mistake.
被法拉利那死胖子利用了
That fat ass Ferrari tricked me.
现在不单抓不到法拉利
We can't catch Ferrari now,
连小脚色也抓不到一个
we can't even catch a fool.
我们现在可以放假了
We are on vacation from now on.
就是嘛，最近几年来大家都很累了
Yes! We have been working real hard this couple of years.
休息一下，好不好？
Let's take a rest, OK?
你该知道怎么办吧？
Do you know what you should do?
我是卧底之王嘛
I am the king of undercover cops.
我现在是黑锅之王
Now I'm the king of scapegoats.
真的是我，我没有化妆
It's the real me! I didn't put on a mask.
你放下你的证件和配枪休息一下吧
Put down your ID and your gun and take a vacation.
上车
Get in the car.
你告诉我，昨晚你到底去了哪里？
Tell me, where did you go last night?
你知不知道我多担心
Do you know I was very worried about you?
我为了你，连工作都没有了
Because of you, I lost my job too.
你别哭了，到底发生了什么事？
Don't cry, what happened?
连你都不了解我
You don't understand me too.
你别抱得我那么紧，我怕失去控制
Don't hold me so tight. I might lose control.
你到底喜欢我吗？
Do you like me?
你这样问是不是太直接了？
Isn't this a little too straight forward?
你欺负我      没有
- You pick on me. - No.
你当我是妓女？
You think I am a hooker?
不是
No!
我知道你不会的，你等我一会儿
I know you won't. Wait for me.
我的上帝，你突然间…
My God, you suddenly give me two girls with huge breasts.
给我两个胸脯那么丰满的女人
我吃不消的
I really can't take it.
你别看我外表很强壮似的
I look very strong,
其实，我每天晚上要撒七八次尿
but I go to the bathroom 7-8 times a night.
给你一分钟
I will give you one minute.
我出来的时候，不想见你还穿着衣服
When I come out, I don't want you to be wearing anything.
已接到画面了
I've got the picture.
C组在慈云山干扰电视台的电波
Group C, start interrupting the signal to the TV station.
别为那个臭男人伤心了
Forget about that asshole.
打打麻将多开心
Let's play mahjong.
自摸
I won!
又自摸了，多开心
What a happiness!
你男朋友正在电视里跳脱衣舞呢
Your boyfriend is strip dancing on TV.
不会吧？
No way?
真的是他
It's him!
身材不错
He's got a great body.
露屁股
Let me see his ass.
干嘛？不用干活吗？
What? Get to work?
身材不错
Nice body!
那混旦怎么很像我
That asshole does look like me.
你叫我脱衣服，怎么你又穿衣服呢
You told me to take off my clothes, but why are you still wearing yours?
因为…
Because...
长毛、大强，你们两个…
Long Hair, Ken, we have been friends for so long.
是从小跟我一起长大的好兄弟
这次，我只想你们两个公正
Tell me the truth.
坦白地告诉我
我戴了帽子和眼镜之后
After I put on this hat and glasses,
还有人会认得我吗？
can people still recognize me?
长毛
Long Hair.
不认识…
No...
大强
Ken.
不认识…
No...
我黏上胡子会不会好点？
Will it be better if I put some mustache on?
好，Pizza都认不出你了，是吗？
OK! Even Pizza won't recognize you, right?
是
Yes!
我决定自杀，我没脸见Pizza
I decided to commit suicide. I don't dare to see Pizza again.
不过在我死之前，我决定…
But before I die, I have decided...
先解决你们两个混旦
I am going to kill you both!
你不要管我，我没脸见你
Don't mind me, I am useless.
你是不是一个男人？
Are you a man?
我是男人
I am a man.
全香港的人都知道我是男人
Everybody in Hong Kong knows that I am a man.
不过是一个不知廉耻的男人
But, I am a shithead.
你就这样放弃？
You are going to give up like this?
如果你现在放弃的话
If you give up,
你永远就是一个大笨旦
you will be a fool forever!
只有赢回那个法拉利和初恋
You have to defeat Ferrari and First Love.
你才能抬起头做人
Then you will become a true man again.
我斗不过他们的
I can't beat them.
只有一个人可以帮你
Only one person can help you.
是谁？
Who?
我姐夫，黄师虎
My brother-in-law, Master Wong.
世事无绝对
Don't worry about it,
偶尔输一次没什么大不了
everybody will lose once or twice.
我在意志最消沉的时候
When my life is heading downhill.
难得Pizza不怪我花心而原谅了我
It's sweet that Pizza has forgiven me.
更鼓励我去复仇
She even tells me to seek revenge.
所以我决定听她的话，去澳门
So I've decided to listen to her and go to Macau.
找她姐夫
And go look for her brother-in-law.
什么？要我教他？
What? You want me to teach him?
行，你叫他来找我吧
OK, tell him to come look for me.
明天买第二场一号“万佛朝宗”吗？
In tomorrow's horse race, bet on "Super" on the 2nd race?
让我再想一想，你先出去
Let me think. Can you go out first?
是
Yes!
Pinky，今天两点半那约会帮我取消
Pinky, cancel the meeting at 2:30 today.
另外叫小志雄拿一碗猪骨粥给我吃
And tell Chi Hon to get me a bowl of pigbone congee.
记得叫他进来时先要敲门
Tell him to knock before he comes in.
抢东西
Thief.
我是抢匪，快来抓我
I am a thief, come catch me.
神经病
Crazy!
叫警察抓我…
Tell the police to catch me...
你干什么？
What are you doing?
抢你的钱包
I want your purse.
你看，我抢了十几个钱包
Look, no one arrests me even I robbed over ten purses.
都没有人来抓我，怎么办呢？
What should I do?
救命，非礼
Help! Rape!
去死吧…
Go to hell...
看什么看？
What are you looking at?
警察先生，见到我师父吗？
Sir, do you know where my master is?
谁是你的师父？
Who is your master?
千王之王，黄师虎
The King of Swindlers, Master Wong.
黄师虎？      是
- Master Wong? - Yes!
他刚出狱了
He just got released.
黄师虎
Master Wong.
我先出去了，你好好过活吧
I am leaving now, take your time in there.
出来再找我，保重了
Come look for me again when you are released. Take care.
不要，你救我出去吧
No! Come save me.
黄师虎，你快回来
Master Wong, come back.
别过来…
Don't come any closer...
黄师虎…救命…
Master Wong...Help...
二万      碰
- Twenty thousands. - I want it!
六婶，你怎么了？三太公十二张
Aunt Six, what's the matter? Watch out!
一筒
One circle.
一筒就平安无事
It should be fine.
大四喜门前清对对糊混一色、五暗坎
I win. It's a big slam...
五个花，一百六十番，三太公
160 fold! Grandpa Sam.
三太公…
Grandpa Sam...
请你给了钱再晕好不好？
Can you pay before you faint?
我去厕所
I need to use the bathroom.
三太公…
Grandpa Sam...
怎么样？摆好了吗？
So, ready?
等你      开吧
- We are waiting for you. - Let's go!
三只King头，同花顺二关，同花顺尾
Three Kings, straight flush in the middle and on the last row.
三只头，二俘虏二关，四条Ace押尾
Three of a kind, full house in the middle, four aces on the last row.
三只三头，四俘虏二关，四条七押尾
Three of a kind, full house of 4, four sevens at the end.
一对…两对…顺子？
One pair...Two pairs...Straight?
只得一对，两对和顺子？
One pair, two pair and straight?
真棒，你死定了
Yeah! You are dead!
等一等
Wait.
还是顺子顺子顺子吧
All straight.
三关都是顺子，例牌，每位三注
All are straight. Pay up, 3 points each.
我去厕所
I am going to the bathroom.
快点，没人做庄，我来
Hurry. No one wants to be a dealer, I will do it.
快下注…打什么牌头好呢？
Hurry...
你那么旺，有种就打个摩天大厦出来
What should I deal first?
等一等，过一幢
Wait. Pass.
十一
Eleven.
你干什么？
What're you doing?
我去厕所
I need to use the bathroom.
双天至尊
Super Twins!
来吧…
Come on...
来      来吧
- Come on... - Come on.
又输了
You lose!
别赢得太尽好不好？
You don't have to win too much!
太哥，我刚从监狱出来
Sir, I just got out of jail.
算是给我一条生路走走吧      老公
- Let me win some money, OK. - Honey.
我要尿尿
I need to piss.
老公，帮帮阿宽吧，他好可怜
Honey, help Leung, he is very sad.
别浪费我时间好不好？
Stop wasting my time, OK?
姐夫，阿宽在监狱里
Brother-in-law, Leung suffered badly in jail.
真的被人欺负得很惨
有多惨？
How badly?
他们简直不是人
They are not human beings.
他们在我身上
On my body,
留下一个永远不能磨灭的痕迹
they tattooed a nasty mark!
你被他们搞过？
Did they rape you?
五个人按着我，六、七个人搞我
Five men held me down. Six, seven people raped me.
看看
Look.
别看，走
Don't look, let's go.
你别这样
Don't be like this.
不要看，太难看了
Don't look, it's nasty.
你坚强一点，让我姐夫看看
Be strong. Let him see it.
大家一起过来看看吧
Everybody come take a look.
六婶来吧
Aunt Six, come on!
B仔过来看，阿姨给你钱…
B boy, come take a look, aunt will give you money.
你想不想报仇？
Do you want to seek revenge?
转过来
Turn around!
(我爱蔡枫华)
"I love Ken Choi"
蔡枫华？怎么搞的？
You like Ken Choi? What the hell?
那又怎么样？蔡枫华有什么问题？
So what? What's wrong with Ken Choi?
没有，他不错的
Nothing, he is quite handsome.
是，蔡枫华有什么问题呢？没事了…
Yes, what is wrong with Ken Choi? Nothing...
糟了
My god!
老公
Honey.
混旦，你那么恨法拉利
Asshole! You hate Ferrari so much,
你就教个徒弟出来打败他
then train a student to kick his ass.
省着点吧，等他学会也要二、三十年
Save your breath. If I teach him, it will at least take 20 to 30 years.
那时候，法拉利不死他都死了
By then, Ferrari will be dead.
你那么有本事怎么你又不去打败他呢
Then why don't you go challenge him?
是…
Yes...
好，要我出山，先拿一千万首期吧
I'll come out from seclusion but I need $10,000,000 as deposit.
我哪有那么多钱？
I don't have that much.
没钱就早点说嘛，别走得那么近
You should have told me earlier. Don't come any closer.
我也不是完全没有
I do have some money.
我身上还有几万块的
I do have a little.
拿来看看
Show me.
真是只有几万块钱
Only a little.
你只得几块钱就说成几万块
You only have couple of dollars.
居然想骗我，看来你有做老千的潜质
You lied to me, you have what it takes to become a true swindler.
是吗？
Really?
我是不是很帅？
Am I handsome?
非常帅      你呢
- Of course. - What about you?
比你更帅
I am more handsome than you.
你连自己都骗
You lied to yourself.
这是做老千的先决条件
You have to do that to become a true swindler.
那就太好了
That's great.
师虎，你快教我几招把戏好不好？
Master Wong, can you show me some of your skills?
先舔我鞋底再说吧
Lick my shoe clean first.
又要舔？
Again?
既然这样，我只好教你一下
I think I will teach you a little bit then.
谢谢师虎
Thanks, Master Wong.
不错，那小子在那屋里几天没出来
Yes, that kid has been in that house for couple of days.
他去找谁？
Who is he visiting?
不知道，听说他想找一个人帮他报仇
I don't know! I heard that he's asking a man to help him seek revenge.
澳门只有一个叫黄师虎的有点能耐
There is a Master Wong who is rather famous.
不过我没见过他
But I haven't seen him before.
那么该怎么办呢？老板
What should I do, boss?
我不大想见他，帮我解决他吧
I don't want to see him. Help me put him away.
你们三个，这种球技怎能代表日本？
You three, how can you be representatives of Japan?
我命中注定，一生命犯天煞孤星
I'm predestinated to be an orphan,
孤独无儿，输死到老
that I will be alone for my whole life.
作为一个老千，现在你算是有点气势
As a swindler, you now have a strong force around you.
再弄快点
Faster.
这就行了
This will do.
法拉利要是见到他还不让他吓傻了眼
Ferrari will be scared when he sees you like this.
师虎，这只是拍电影时骗人的把戏
Master, this only can be used in the movies.
你教我点实在的绝招好不好？
Can you teach me some practical tricks?
说明速成的，这已经是最绝的了
This is fast and powerful.
别生气了
Don't get mad.
师虎，你出山吧
Master, please come out from seclusion and help.
可以，一千万按金，三个月上期
OK! $10,000,000 as deposit, three month's prepayment.
你老说一千万，我只有几十块
Stop saying $10,000,000, I only have a little money.
我看，几十块你都没有
I don't think you have any money left.
本来是有的
I do before.
但是回来的时候，买了一包香烟
But on the way back, you bought a pack of cigarette.
怎么你什么都知道呢？
How do you know that?
你哪能骗得了我？
You can't trick me.
这样吧
So if I can trick you,
如果我骗到你是不是什么都行？
then I can ask you to do whatever I want?
什么都行
Whatever you want!
出山行不行？      行
- Will you come out from seclusion? - OK!
你发誓吧
You swear.
如果你骗到我，我就出山
If you can trick me, I will come out from seclusion.
好
OK.
不要…
Please don't...
师母，很久不见，原来你是竹笋型的
Ma'am, haven't seen you for ages, I don't know you've got big breasts.
那还用说
Of course.
吻我的乳头
Kiss my nipple.
你也吻我
You kiss me too.
怎么没有反应呢？
How come there is no reactions?
我想，他可能去了厨房拿刀来砍我
I think he is going to the kitchen to get a knife to kill me.
你这混旦，还未闯进来？
Bastard, how dare you don't break in?
怎么你这么冷静？
How come you are so calm?
你别这么傻了，竹笋型几时轮到你
Don't be silly, you don't have big breasts.
我就是竹笋型嘛      你是飞机场
- I do. - You have little breast.
小丈夫
You scam!
卡住了，帮帮忙吧
I am clipped between, please come and help.
你真够笨
You are so stupid!
骗人也要动动脑子
Use your brain!
走吧，回家再想到好办法才来吧
Leave, go home and think of something better.
怎么搞的？再请几个人来
What? You think that you hire couple of hitmen and it will do?
套个大头佛这就叫好办法？
你只拿个锤？大哥，下点本钱吧
You only carry a hammer? Man, put more money into your budget.
对了，起码有一支玩具枪才像样
Right! At least get a toy gun!
是真家伙
It's real!
出去吧
Get out.
老公…你没事吧？老公，你怎么样？
Honey, are you OK? Honey, how are you?
我没事
I am OK!
不要再多说了，我们走吧
Stop it, let's go.
去哪里？
Where?
回香港，这次我要亲自找法拉利算帐
Go back to Hong Kong. I'll go visit Ferrari and seek revenge myself.
太好了
Yeah! It's great!
老婆，到香港之后
Honey, when we get to Hong Kong...
顺便买颗钻石戒指给你做生日
I will buy you a diamond ring for your birthday.
你别吓我
Don't try to scare me.
你从来没买过超过两百块的礼物给我
You never buy me anything which is worth more than $200.
走吧
Let's go.
我不要…救命
I don't want it...Help.
姐夫说得对，我也要买颗钻石戒指
Brother-in-law is right. I want a diamond too.
你那么贪心，早晚你也会发神经的
Don't be so greedy, or you'll get crazy!
别生气嘛，为求押韵而已
Don't get mad! It's just a joke.
特别消息，本港富商郑一筒先生
Special news. Mr. Cheng Yat-tone, a billionaire of Hong Kong,
还有非常有生意头脑的
and the famous merchant Mr. Ho Lin.
被人称为“谂伯”的何林先生
两位已经失踪了一个星期
Both of them have been missing for a week.
外间推测他们被绑架了…
People suspect that they might be kidnapped...
你姐夫录了这段新闻
Your brother-in-law recorded this part of the news.
这两天已看了一百多次
He has watched it over a hundred times.
还要我看一百多次，等他回来
He wants me to watch it a hundred times until he comes back.
告诉他有什么巧妙
And he wants me to tell him what I think about this.
他就是神神秘秘的
I can tell something mysterious.
警方到目前为止，有什么重要线索呢
Is there any lead to this case?
秘密
Confidential.
警方有没有抓到些可疑人物呢？
Did the police arrest any suspect?
也是秘密
Confidential.
我说，他可能是存心戏弄我
I said, he is trying to play me.
你耐心点吧
Be patient.
也许过两天
May be in a couple of days,
他会教你一招半式的出千绝招呢
he will teach you couple of his tricks.
老公
Honey.
Pizza，有没有见到你姐夫？
Pizza, have you seen your brother-in-law?
没有，他不是跟你一起出去了吗？
No! Isn't he with you?
Pizza，你姐夫最近好像有点问题
Pizza, your brother-in-law is acting stranger recently.
我怀疑，他在那天晚上撞坏了脑子
I think that he has damaged his brain on that night.
他怎么了？
What's wrong with him?
带我去买了十几只钻石戒指
He bought me over ten diamond rings.
你…
You...
钻石和黄金，不及我一片真诚与真心
So what, I am true to you.
刚才在买钻石时，走着走着就不见他
While we were shopping, he suddenly disappeared.
我还以为他回来了
I thought he came back already.
今晚八点，到法拉利家里找我
Come to Ferrari's house at eight tonight.
是师虎
It's Master Wong.
李先生，初恋小姐来了
Mr. Lee, First Love is here.
请她进来…
Let her in.
你好
Hello!
对不起，让你久等了
Sorry to let you wait!
坐…
Sit...
怎么那么多保镖呢？
How come you have so many bodyguards?
最近我的老朋友全部都失踪了
Recently, all my friends have been missing.
所以我请多点保镖，以策安全嘛
So I hired more bodyguards to protect me.
出去…      是，李先生
- Get out... - Yes! Mr. Lee.
吃点东西
Have something to eat.
我很害怕
I am scared.
不用怕
Don't worry!
我们唱完歌之后，就上我的游艇去
After we finish singing, we will go to my yacht.
然后开去南丫岛吃海鲜，好吗？
Then we will go to the Lamma Island and eat seafood, OK?
我不能吃海鲜的      为什么？
- I don't like seafood. - Why?
我会皮肤过敏，你看
I am allergic to it, look.
皮肤过敏？
Allergy?
带他回去
Take him back.
老板
Boss.
怎么样？李老板的事办妥了吗？
So, have you finished Lee's job?
办妥了，但是我碰到一个人
Done! But I met a person.
不知道是不是火龙没杀死的那个
I wonder he's the one Lon wasn't able to kill.
他什么模样？
What does he look like?
高高瘦瘦，神神秘秘
Tall and thin, full of secret.
脚跟不着地，样子可恶
He looks nasty!
你讲的那个人除了样子可恶之外
Miss, are you talking about me?
似乎很像是我
就是他，带他回来
It's him, bring him back!
好的
OK.
我好像不认识你的
I don't think I know you.
我来介绍
Let me introduce myself.
人称伤尽万千少女心的千王之王
I am Master Wong...
黄师虎就是我了
who has broken many girls' hearts.
你是好人还是坏人？
Are you a bad guy or a good guy?
坏人
Bad guy!
男人不坏，女人不爱
If a man is not bad, girl won't like him.
可不是嘛，那我就来了
You are right!
你想怎么样？
What do you want?
我想…伤你的心嘛
I want...to break your heart.
好，那就上车吧
OK, get in the car then.
你这车怎么上？还不如上我的车吧
Your car is no good? Why don't you get mine?
好吧，随便你
OK, whatever.
这位就是黄师虎吧？
This is Master Wong, right?
一看阁下的模样，难道就是肉面飞龙
Just by looking at you, are you the Fat Dragon?
这是朋友赏面叫的
Thanks for flatting me.
素仰…
Nice to meet you...
敬佩…      幸会
- My pleasure... - The pleasure is all mine.
素仰
No, it's all mine.
黄师虎，最近有空来香港有什么贵干
Master Wong, so what brings you to Hong Kong?
我专程来向你学习的
I came to learn from you.
真会说笑话
You must be joking.
不是说笑话，素仰阁下赌术精湛
I am not joking. I heard that you're great in gambling.
如有机会赐教小弟，那真是太幸福了
If you can teach me, I will be pleased.
那么，你想学麻将、牌九
So what do you want to learn?
还是大D、沙蟹呢？
就打打小麻将吧
Let's just play mahjong.
怎么打法？肉面飞龙
How do you want to play, Fat Dragon?
台湾牌一、二吧
Taiwan style.
好，一百万底，二十万一番
OK! $1,000,000 as ante, $200,000 per fold.
你有那么多钱吗，黄师虎
Do you have that much money?
汇丰银行本票一千万
A bank draft of $10,000,000.
我相信你
I trust you.
打多少个东？八个？
How many rounds are we going to play? 32?
这样吧
Well...
一个东这么短？
4 rounds?
一把，高手过招
One hand!
一把定输赢好吗？肉面飞龙
We only need one hand to get the winner, OK, Fat Dragon?
好，不愧为千王之王
Good, King of Swindlers, I'm amazed.
过去陪黄师虎打牌
Go keep Master Wong company.
一万
Tenth thousand.
五条
Five bamboos.
红中
Red Dragon.
开杠
Four of a kind.
再开杠
Four of a kind again.
三筒
Three bamboos.
大三元、四番子、四暗坎
It'll be a grand slam!
那就别乱打了
Don't do anything stupid.
是，我要撒尿，不好意思
Yes, I need to use the rest room, excuse me.
一流老千怎会不发觉人家看过他的牌
He's a professional swindler and he'll know that we've peeped at his dominos.
什么牌？
What is it?
有鬼
Ghost!
死三八偷看我的牌，想我干你娘吗？
Bitch! Did you peep at my domino?
怎么样？有没有偷看我的牌？
So? Did you peep at my domino?
没有
No.
来…
Come...
这张牌你一定要的
You want this domino for sure.
害怕就别打
Don't discard it if you are afraid.
我怕你没钱给
I am afraid that you will have no money to pay.
清一色、尼姑尼姑、一般高
I win.
象眼、门前清、一摸五
Thank you, it's a grand slam.
两百番，每每四千一百万
200 folds, everybody pays $41,000,000 please.
你是庄家加一番多二十万
You are the dealer, you have to pay $200,000 more.
不过算了，拿去给佣人吧
But forget it! Give it to your maids.
千王之王果然不是浪得虚名
No wonder you are called the King of Swindler.
肉面飞龙的脸果然很多肉
Fat Dragon is really fat.
你是不是想耍花样？
You want to mess with me?
老公不用怕，我来救你
Don't worry honey, I am here to save you.
你牌技真高…
You've got great skill...
他们怎么那么要好？
How come they look like they are very good friends?
下次有这么好机会记得叫我
Call me if you want to play again.
那就别等下次了
Don't worry, have my invitation now.
我们约定这个星期六赌牌嘛
Let's just play poker this Saturday.
真的吗？赌多大？
Really? What is the bet?
今天都一亿两千了
You won $120,000,000 today.
到那天起码每人五亿吧
Then we have to go at least $500,000,000 on Saturday.
就这么决定
OK.
你姐夫他是很难捉摸的
Your brother-in-law is hard to understand.
签了这份合约，不来也要输五亿
Sign this contract, if you don't come you've to lose $500,000,000 too.
好，阿宽
OK! Leung.
来了
Coming.
你签      好的
- Sign it. - OK.
老婆，我刚才赢了一亿多元
Honey. I just won $120,000,000 tonight.
再买几个宝石戒指给你
I will buy you couple more diamond rings.
我不要，你干什么？
I don't want it, what are you doing?
我就是要买给你
I am going to buy it.
救命…我不要
Help...I don't want it.
我永远都不会忘记
I will never forget what we have done tonight.
今晚我们所做的一切
嫂子，我们什么都没做过
Ma'am, we didn't do anything.
没做过？你好
Nothing? How dare you?
我要自杀、我要跳楼
I am going to commit suicide. I am going to jump.
你和那个女人有一腿
You are having an affair with that woman!
大姐你别这样
Sister, don't be like this.
姐夫，你说句话好不好
Brother-in-law, will you say something please?
她要跳楼，她真的会跳楼的
She wants to jump, she really wants to jump.
那个女人分明在搞事
Even a fool knows that she is trying to mess up.
她要是相信那就让她去死好了
If she wants to believe it then let her die.
等我再赢法拉利五亿元之后
After I won that $500,000,000,
就便宜其他女人
I will go find some other girls.
没那么容易，我不会死的
No way, I am not going to jump.
那就快去煮点甜品给我吃吧
Go get me some dessert.
你休想便宜其他女人
Don't you dare have another woman.
你真的以为法拉利想再和我赌？
You really think that Ferrari will bet with me again?
合约我已经签了
I signed the contract already.
合约我让你来签
You signed it for me.
他这样都肯就知道不是真的了
He let me do that which means that is not real.
我还查到他旗下的公司
I also found out that all the company under his name...
最近沽了两万几张期指
he sold 20,000 pieces of dealings in future.
香港三大富豪又失踪了
Three of the richest men in Hong Kong have disappeared.
我想绝大可能是给他抓了
I think he must have kidnapped them,
逼他们把股价压低
to force the stock market to drop.
搞垮香港股市来赚钱
And use this advantage to make tons of money.
这才是真正的大老千
He is a real good swindler.
约我去赌钱，只是想拖延时间
He asked me to play on Saturday because he wants a delay.
让我这几天去筹钱不用骚扰他
I will be trying to gather enough money and thus leave him alone.
然后在期指市场赚大钱
Then he will be making tons of money in the stock market.
那要不要报警？
Should we call the police?
如果报警，那几个大富豪就危险了
If we do, those rich men will be in danger.
那怎么办？      是
- What should we do? - Yes!
超哥，穿了黑衣黑裤黑领带
Bill, after I put on this black suit, pants and tie,
像不像黑社会？
do I look like a gangster!
你根本是黑社会嘛
You are a gangster!
不是，我是福建大学毕业的
No way! I graduated from Fukien University.
找不到工作才来这里找事做
I can't find any work so I came here to work.
你识字的吗？
Do you know how to read?
识，不过穿成这样，会给人家打吗？
Yes! But if I dress like this, will I get beaten up?
这个…在所难免了
This...You can't avoid it.
不会吧？
No way?
(树后没有人)
"There is nobody behind the tree."
大学生，写什么？
U graduate student, what does it say?
树后没有人
There is nobody behind the tree.
真够笨
Idiot!
大哥，我经过这里想借个厕所
Boss, I just want to use your restroom.
用不着用这么多镭射电光枪吧
You don't have to point so many lazar guns at me.
笨旦，我老板说烧了你的屋子
Stupid! My boss told us to burn down your house.
知道你无家可归
We know that you will be homeless.
所以准备了总统套房让你住
So we have prepared the presidential suite for you.
带他去吧
Take him there.
林伯，你好…
Uncle Lin, hello!
筒哥，真够巧的
Brother Tone, nice to meet you.
诚哥，真的很久不见了
Mr. Lee, long time no see.
最近楼市怎么样？
How is the real estate business doing recently?
你是哪一位？
Who are you?
我和你们一样，都是被人抓进来的
I am like you guys, I have been kidnapped.
你可别把我们和你相提并论
We are not like you.
进得这间屋子的个个都家财几百亿
Each of us possesses at least couple hundreds billions.
你有吗？
Do you have it?
过了明晚你们就没有了
After tomorrow night, you won't.
今天恒指又跌三千几点
Today the stock market dropped 3,000 points.
后天等我平了期指合约
I'll sell everything the day after tomorrow,
我就有几百亿了
then I will gain couple hundred billions.
我要是能够出去
If I can get out.
我一定叫我的电视台谴责你
I will talk so much shit about you on my television station.
你那个电视台都没人看的
No one watches your station.
给他们吃点消夜
Give them their late night snacks.
不，我们不吃了，救命…
No, we don't want it, help...
有消夜吃还叫救命？真搞不懂你们
Why are you screaming? You don't like late night snacks?
不是的，他每餐都给我们吃伟哥
No! They gave us Viagra every meal.
我们饿了几顿了
We haven't eaten anything for a long time.
肚子里一点东西都没有
真险毒
What an evil man!
这几天连蟑螂都没有，我们快饿死了
There're no cockroaches found in these few days. We're starving to death.
我真聪明
I am very smart.
刚才我在外面见到一条鳄鱼
I caught a small crocodile outside earlier.
我乘他们不防把它藏起来了
I hide it inside my shirt.
这是壁虎
It's a house lizard.
同类嘛，鳄鱼是很补的
No, a crocodile is nutritious.
给我…
Give it to me...
不行…
No.
我给你一百万，你给我吃      真的？
- I'll give you a million, give it to me. - Really?
我给一千万
I will give you ten million.
静一静，我给你十间“浆糊山庄”
Quiet! I will give you ten flats,
你给我吃
let me have it.
这算什么？
I'll give you ten better flats!
我给你十间“牛腱阁”单位
真的吗？      是真的
- Really? - Yes.
真的才好说
Keep your words then.
我把电视台全给你
I will give you my TV station.
我知道你很有同情心的，是吧？
I know you are very kind, right?
那倒是的，林伯，那就给你吧
Right. Uncle Lin, you can have it.
消夜来了
Here comes the late night snacks.
怎么今晚不是吃伟哥吗？
How come it is not Viagra tonight?
老板怕吃得多吃死了你们
Boss is worried about your health.
正点…
Very good!
比鲍鱼更美味
It is better than abalone.
别看了，是你自己求我的
Forget it, you wanted it yourself.
你还欠我一个电视台呢
You still owe me a TV station!
还好你说要，亏本亏死你
How dare you! You will lose all your money.
姐夫两天没回来了
Brother-in-law hasn't come home for two days already,
要不要到法拉利家去救他？
should we go save him?
今晚还约了法拉利赌牌
We have to play poker with Ferrari tonight.
就算不去，也要输五亿
If we don't go, we will lose $500,000,000 dollars too.
那合约是你签的
You signed the contract.
现在没办法了，他一定是被人抓了
We are running out of time, he must be captured.
我一定要上门去救他
I have to go save him.
怎么救？
How?
你代替你师父赌
Gamble for your master.
不是吧？
No way!
站好
Get up straight.
筒哥，你的手不要挡住，放下来
Brother Tone, don't cover it, come on.
好了，大家有点笑容，预备
OK, smile a little, ready.
谢谢了，大家可以穿衣服了
Thanks, you guys can put on your clothes now.
诚哥，玩十二五十
Mr. Lee, you lost 20 flats to me.
你输了二十层浆糊山庄给我，你记住
筒哥，我们摔跤
Mr. Tone, you lost 10 flats to me.
你输了十层牛腱阁单位给我
你是个人物，不会赖帐吧
You are well known, don't try to run.
林伯，我跟你撒尿斗远，你又输了
Uncle Lin, you lost in the contest of who can pee farther.
是你输给我
No, you lost.
对不起，我记错了
Sorry! I remember it wrong.
我们会给你钱的，你用不着拍照
We will pay you, you don't have to take pictures.
你是想勒索吧？
Are you trying to blackmail us?
你怎么这样看我？
How can you think of me that way?
我们今天能相聚总算是缘分
It is faith that brought us together.
拍个照只不过想留个纪念
I just want to treasure this moment.
大家千万别误会
Please don't get me wrong.
老板
Boss,
明天香港股市一开只剩三、四千点
the stock market will be opened at 3 or 4 thousand points,
你那两万张期指就赚大钱了
you'll gain a fortune.
为什么今晚还要跟他赌呢？
Why are you still going to bet with him?
就算黄师虎没给我抓到
Even if we don't have Master Wong in our hands,
只要我出动手上最高科技的产品
just by using our secret weapon,
这五亿元我赢定他的，我怕什么呢？
I will win his $500,000,000 for sure. Why should I worry?
老板，你有什么绝招？
Boss, what is your secret weapon?
就是这个DV机和我这副眼镜
It's that DV machine and my glasses.
肥猪王，你在后面用DV机看我的牌
Fat Pig, use the DV machine to look at my card.
这么远都管用吗？
Will it work from this far?
你用这副眼镜坐在我对面看
Wear this glasses and sit opposite to me.
是，老板
Yes, boss!
老板，你的底牌是King
Boss, you have a king.
真厉害，老板
It's awesome, boss!
我戴着这副眼镜
Wearing this pair of glasses.
他每一把的底牌我都看见
I can see any of his cards.
我还怕什么呢？
Why should I worry?
那就一定要赌
We have to play with him then.
快准备一下，客人就要到了
Go get ready, our guesses are almost here.
是，老板
Yes! Boss!
黄师虎呢？
Where is Master Wong?
什么师虎？
Who?
你不知道吗？今晚由我唱独脚戏
You don't know? I come alone tonight.
你的头发真漂亮
Your hair is very pretty.
看你的嘴巴多甜
Stop sweet talking.
现在七点，我们定时三个小时
It's 7 o'clock right now. We will play for three hours.
到了十点，你就算输一块钱
At 10 o'clock, even if you lose one dollar,
也要输光五亿
you will lose all of your $500,000,000.
钱？
Where is the money?
不是链，是钱，美女
Not your necklace. It's money, silly!
那么多钱…
So much money...
一会过来跟你聊天，慢慢看吧
I will talk to you later.
黄师虎的老婆和小姨不见了
Master Wong's wife and his sister-in-law is missing.
我看她们有阴谋，你去看看
There must be a conspiracy, go check it out.
明白
Got you.
开始了好吗？
Can we begin?
我去一去洗手间
I need to use the restroom.
我要拉屎那又怎办？
What if I need to stool?
我还是先忍一忍
I think I will wait.
发牌
Deal it!
妈的，屋子这么大，怎么找呢？
Damn! This house is so big, how are we going to find him?
就是嘛      真是的
- You are right! - Damn!
有人
Somebody is over there.
今晚拉哥开赌局
Tonight Ferrari is gambling inside,
看来花园一定没有人
no one will stay in the garden.
谁说没有人
Who said that?
三个富豪在哪儿？
Where are the rich men?
在地牢里
They are in the basement.
说了还要打？
Why did you hit me?
你穿黑衣黑裤子像个黑社会
You look like a gangster,
还不应该打吗？
that's why I hit you.
去死吧
Go the hell!
还是换个衣服安全点
lt'll be safe to get changed.
大家小注怡情吧，我出一千元
Let's bet small, $1,000.
对不起，规矩是最少十万
Sorry! The rule state that you must bet at least $100,000.
听说你不会赌钱的
I heard that you don't know how to gamble.
不要每一把都向我梭哈，这一招不灵
Don't try to show hand on every hand! This won't work on me.
你尽管放心，我不会轻易梭哈的
Don't worry, I don't like to show hand this easily.
顺你的意，小一点，一百万吧
Up to you, let's go smaller. One million.
不玩
Quit.
怎么回事？这还嫌大
What the hell? Too big for you?
你别吃
Stop it!
大姐，好像是姐夫
Sister, I heard the voice of brother-in-law!
老公
Honey.
你是谁？      是贼
- Who are you? - A thief.
老公
Honey.
老婆？
Honey?
老公
Honey.
怎么那么巧？
What a coincidence?
快找钥匙来
Go find the key.
这两位是…
They are...
这是我老婆，那是我小姨子
This is my wife, this is my sister-in-law.
有兴趣吗？
Interested?
我小姨只要十层浆糊山庄就可以商量
My sister-in-law is worth ten flats of "High Class" estates.
你太太呢？
What about your wife?
诚哥你一句话
Mr. Lee, because of you.
她嘛，两层大陆碧桂园你就拿去吧
How about two flats?
一层？
One?
你给首期我供楼
Just give me the down payment.
原来放在后面
It's at his back.
找到了
Found it.
钥匙在我这里
I've got the key.
你这贱人
You bitch!
姐妹同心，一起收拾她
Let's take care of her, sister.
快捡起来…
Pick it up...
现在的狐狸精真会打架
Bitches these days do know how to fight.
贱人，你是哪里人？
Woman, where are you from?
上海
Shanghai.
好姐妹
Good, my dear sister!
用手帕看看行不行
Let's try to use the handkerchief.
快点
Hurry.
你的J大，你说吧
Your Jack is bigger, go ahead.
让你说      五十万
- Pass. - $500,000.
不玩了
Quit.
你要不要？
Are you going to go?
不玩
No.
你要不要？
Are you going?
不玩…
No...
看来你又不要了？
You are not going to go?
不要了
No.
(不要)
"No."
你每一把都不要，什么意思？
You didn't play every hand, what the hell is wrong with you?
难道不要也不行吗？
Do I have to play every hand?
你以为我不用输钱吗？
I have to lose money too!
大哥，十万元一把
You know it is $100,000 a hand.
老板，他好像想拖延时间
Boss, looks like he is trying to waste time.
五亿元怎么输？
He's plenty to lose.
初恋去了很久没回来，你去看看
First Love has gone for too long, go check on her.
有什么事就…
If anything happens, then...
痛不痛？
Does it hurts?
你们两个人，钥匙又抢不过我
You two can't take the key from me.
打也打不过我
You two can't beat me.
挖个洞死了就算
Just did a hole and die, OK?
大姐，打死她
Sister, hit her.
让你试试大老婆的厉害
Let me show you my power.
只差一点点而已…
Almost there...
你这贱人，连钥匙也要吞
You bitch, how dare you swallow the key?
你快吐出去
Spit it out.
否则剖开你的肚子
Or I will cut your stomach.
你想怎么样？
What do you want?
那你想怎么样？
你怎么出来的？
How did you escape?
这种锁我用一个万字夹就开了
I can open this kind of lock with a clipper.
你早点说嘛，害得我打得一身汗
You should have told me earlier! So I don't have to fight so hard.
谁叫你打的？
Who told you to fight?
阿宽在帮你赌
Leung is gambling for you.
印度帝景园一层，你考虑吗？
India Garden, one flat, deal?
要两层
Two flats?
你给首期，我供吧
You pay the down payment, I will pay the rest.
卷发小子，你尽管玩
Smart-ass, keep fooling around.
现在我比你多几百万
I've had couple millions more than you.
一到十点我就数钱
At 10 o'clock I will start to count your money.
你输一元也算输五亿了
Even you lose one dollar, you will lose all your $500,000,000.
你少管我，一会儿我去洗个澡
Don't mind me! I have to go take a shower later.
十点还早
It's still early.
现在九点四十分了，这个钟停了而已
It's 9:40 now. The clock stopped by itself.
你尽管拖
In 20 minutes you will lose all of your $500,000,000.
还有二十分钟你就输光面前的五亿元
你是谁？没见过你的
Who are you? I haven't seen you before.
每逢赶时间你这家伙总是站着挡路
Every time I am in a hurry you just have to be in my way.
三个老家伙在哪儿？
Where are the old fools?
坐的士走了
They left by taking a taxi.
那你就坐灵车吧
You will be going home in a funeral car.
换了女人衣服，一定不会再被人打了
I have changed into woman's clothes, no one will hit me.
我从来没见过这么丑的女人
I never seen woman this ugly before.
一千万
$10,000,000.
梁先生，你要不要？
Mr. Leung, are you going to go?
你到底要不要？
Are you going to go?
那么少，怎么要？
Not big enough!
嫌少？多少你才肯要？
How big do you want?
起码五千万吧
At least $50,000,000.
好，就五千万
OK, $50,000,000.
五千万那就…
$50,000,000 then...
他说要
He will go!
师虎，你来了，快坐下吧      当然了
- Master, sit down. - Of course.
跟你五千万，看牌
I will go with your $50,000,000. Card.
黄师虎，这一把你不能看，是他在赌
Master Wong, you can't play this hand. It's him who is gambling.
谁说的？
Who said so?
我说的
I did!
这一把已经开始就一定要梁先生赌完
Mr. Leung should go on with this game.
阁下是…
You're...
我是国际赌协会长兼环球赌协委员
I'm the Chairman of the International Gambling Association.
三届澳门荣誉董事
And...
兼越南、柬甫寨和…      够了…
- I've been the honored director... - Enough!
今天渥此为止，明天再跟你赌
Let's stop right now, we'll gamble tomorrow.
好的
OK.
不赌也行
If you leave now,
不过照规矩，你要输光五亿了
you will lose $500,000,000.
那算什么意思？
What the hell?
一定要我赌？
I have to play this hand?
这…这些钱是谁的？
Whose money is this?
你的，我卖了所有的家当跟他赌
Yours! I sold all your property.
老公
Honey.
师虎
Master.
怎么办？
What should we do?
赌吧，不然钱都没了
Play it, or I will lose my money.
你们别再演戏了，到底要不要？
Stop acting. Are you going or not?
赌吧，你行的
Go! You can make it.
好，跟你五千万，跟着梭哈
OK, I will go and I will show hand too.
死也就一把而已
It is only one hand.
就跟你赌一把
Just a game, win or die.
原来他的底牌是King
His covered card is a King.
怎么样小子？
What is it?
我的牌面比你大，发牌吧
My hand is bigger that yours. Card!
想赢我，除非全是红心花吧
If you want to win, unless you have all hearts.
难道他是顺子？
Does he have a straight?
博不到了吧
You can't make it, right?
在我这里
I've got yours.
他一定没有顺子
He doesn't have a straight.
你也一样没有花
You don't have a straight.
小子，你跟了千王之王这么久
Kid, you learned from the King of Swindlers for so long,
学了点什么赌术？
what have you got?
我Ace一对，看你怎么赢我
I have a pair of Ace, let's see how you can beat me.
我也是Ace一对
I have a pair of Ace too,
不过我Ace一对配Q
but my pair goes with a pair of queen.
你Ace一对就配个10
Your pair goes with a pair of 10.
怎么都比你大，死胖子
Mine is bigger than yours, fat boy.
好棒…
Very good...
不可能的，你出老千
No way, you cheated.
你的底牌明明是…
Your card is...
怎么不是King吗？
How come it is not a king?
我后面的死胖子看了一晚眼都花了
That fat boy's eyes are very tired after a whole night of work.
他看到的不是我的牌
What he saw was not my card.
是我十只手指而已
But my fingers.
不是Ace一对的话我怎么会要呢？
Why should I go if I don't have a pair of Ace?
你真是神经病
You must be crazy!
你的科技两年前我已经不用了
I quit using your technology two years ago.
太落伍了
You are out-dated.
师虎，你这招真的行
Master, your trick worked.
当然嘛，他以为你赌就一定会赢你
Of course, he thought that he would bet you for sure.
否则，又怎么会乖乖地坐在这儿
If not, why would he sit there...
输五亿给我呢
and lose $500,000,000 to me?
真是大笨旦
What an idiot!
这无所谓，这儿区区五亿，给你吧
So what, I will give you $500,000,000.
明天一早，我就有五百亿了
But I will have 50 billion early tomorrow morning.
那可不是
I don't think so!
我和全香港的富豪，以及政府
I tell you the truth! Within 25 minutes,
在二十五分钟里狂扫股市
the HK stocks in London raised 10,000 points...
在收市之前
because the billionaires...
伦敦港股指数，已经上升了一万点
and the government allied to push it up.
现在是一万六千点
The reading is 16,000 points now.
你在说谎
You are lying.
你的同党也跟你窝里反，转买期指
Your fellows betrayed you to buy in stocks too.
你的期指合约，明天大概要输一百亿
I think you'll lose 10 billions instead.
你们这些混旦
You assholes!
(动他)
"Kick his butt!"
闪开
Move!
他干嘛？他想怎么样？
What is he doing?
这招就是失传了一百年的肥螳螂？
This is the long lost kung fu, Fat Mantis?
肥螳螂？
Fat Mantis?
不就是螳螂拳中最毒辣的一招？
Isn't this move most powerful?
还杀人不见血呢      是
- It kills without blood. - Yes!
阿宽，你真行
Leung, you are good!
这种场面
I wish my boss the Masked-man will see this scene.
要是让我上司千面人见到就好了
我不会令你失望的
I won't disappoint you.
阿宽，你可以继续做卧底了
Leung, you can continue to be an undercover.
我还帮你做卧底？
No way!
我拿着五亿元
I have $500,000,000 dollars now,
买颗大钻石给我Pizza，和她…好吗
I will buy Pizza a big diamond and...OK?
你终于肯买钻石戒指给我了吗？
You finally want to buy me a diamond ring?
当然了
Of course!
不管爱得有多深，买粒钻石表真心嘛
No matter how deep my love is to you, only a diamond can prove.
老公，你把五亿全给阿宽，我们呢？
Honey, you give all the $500,000,000 to Leung.
这小意思
Don't worry.
我有这三位富豪的写真
I have to naked pictures of the three richest men in Hong Kong,
该不止值五十亿吧？
I think it is worth more than 5 billion.
是吗？那是什么意思？
Really? What do you mean?
就是全走光了
It's all exposed.
我们还有没有五十亿？
Don't we still have 5 billion?
老公…
Honey...
你说会买钻石山给我的
You told me that you will buy a huge diamond hill to me.
刚才不是去过钻石山了吧
We have been to Diamond Hill earlier.
还去了黄大仙，乐富你去不去？
We went to Wong Tai Sin too. Do you want to go to Lok Fu?
梁宽，你太坏了
Leung, you are mean!
干嘛发脾气？
Why are you so mad?
你看看我的手
Look at my hand.
在哪儿修指甲？真漂亮
Where did you get your nails done? It's very pretty.
你答应过买钻石戒指给我的
You promised me to buy me a diamond ring.
你对我情深意重，我怎么会忘记呢？
How can I forget.
你回头看看吧
Turn around.
干什么？
What?
这间宝石店以后就属于你的了
This diamond shop belongs to you.
你别小看这些宝石
Everything here belongs to you.
这些宝石全都是伦敦制造
从歌剧院到青天，从年轻到成年…
Made in London of the opera to the sky from the boys to men.
随便吧
Whatever.
快进去挑吧
Go pick it!
-== 剧 终 ==-
＊＊＊＊＊谢谢观赏＊＊＊＊＊ ＊＊＊＊＊